Anh Hoang Nguyen's Resume

anhnguyen@aaanh.com | https://linkedin.com/in/aaanh | https://github.com/aaanh

Introduction

I actively work on full-stack web applications, micro-service architecture, API development and machine learning research projects in natural language processing (NLP).

I love collaborating with peers and like-minded people to create meaningful projects.

Trotocolorial Exporterior	
M	icrosoft + Nuance (Montreal, QC.)
Software Developer – Internship – (Jan 2023 – May 2023)	
	Developed a new authentication micro-service platform using Nestjs and gRPC.
	Configured and deployed using Kubernetes and Helm.
	Implemented security enhancements for service-to-service connections across clusters with TLS.

SimWell (Laval, QC.)

Software Developer and Architect – MITACS Research Internship – (Jan 2024 – TBD)

☐ Automated patching process for multiple Linux VM nodes with Ansible.

□ Design and develop a distributed, full-stack micro-service architecture for digital twin solution models.

Genetec (Saint-Laurent, QC.)

Professional Experience

Software Developer – Internship – (May 2022 – September 2022)

- ☐ Completed 2 projects involving migration to on-premises Docker container cluster.
- ☐ Created and maintained software build/release pipelines for cross-platform software projects.

IT Specialist – Internship – (August 2021 – December 2021)

 Performed infra and workflow improvements, tested hardware/software compatibility, managed Active Directory and Endpoint, and utilized shell scripting.

Notable Projects

- □ Portfolio Site https://aaanh.ca
- ☐ GPT Web Client https://gpt.aaanh.app
- □ Script Convenience Store https://scripts.aaanh.app
- ☐ GCES Concordia https://gcesconcordia.com

Skills

- $\ \ \, \Box \ \ \, Languages: TypeScript, Java, C, C++, Python, Go, Rust, HTML, CSS, PowerShell, bash.$
- □ Platforms: Linux, Windows, macOS, qemu, Hyper-V, Docker, cri-o, kubernetes, helm, Ansible.
- □ Networking: nginx, calico, caddy, firewalld.
- ☐ Security: (m)TLS, OAuth2, SAML2, jwt, OIDC.
- □ Database: postgres, mysql, CodmosDB, mariadb, redis, memcache.

Volunteering

□ VP of Technology at Gina-Cody School Entrepreneurship Society at Concordia University

Education

- □ Bachelor of Engineering (2020 2024), Concordia University, Montreal, QC.
- □ DEC in Applied Sciences (2017 2020), John Abbott College, Sainte-Anne-de-Bellevue, QC.